export const chapter = "Chapter - 8: Degree of Comparison";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
        {
          question: "What is the Positive Degree of an adjective?",
          optionA: "Describes a Noun or Pronoun in simple terms.",
          optionB: "Compares the quality of one Noun or Pronoun with another.",
          optionC: "Compares a Noun or Pronoun with three or more others.",
          correctAnswer: "Describes a Noun or Pronoun in simple terms.",
        },
        {
          question: "What does the Comparative Degree of an adjective do?",
          optionA: "Describes a Noun or Pronoun in simple terms.",
          optionB: "Compares the quality of one Noun or Pronoun with another.",
          optionC: "Compares a Noun or Pronoun with three or more others.",
          correctAnswer:
            "Compares the quality of one Noun or Pronoun with another.",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In the sentence 'Raghu is poorer than Radhe,' what degree of adjective is used for 'poor'?",
          optionA: "Positive Degree",
          optionB: "Comparative Degree",
          optionC: "Superlative Degree",
          correctAnswer: "Comparative Degree",
        },
        {
          question: "What is the Superlative Degree of an adjective used for?",
          optionA: "Describes a Noun or Pronoun in simple terms.",
          optionB: "Compares the quality of one Noun or Pronoun with another.",
          optionC:
            "Compares a Noun or Pronoun with three or more others, indicating the maximum quality.",
          correctAnswer:
            "Compares a Noun or Pronoun with three or more others, indicating the maximum quality.",
        },
        {
          question:
            "How are most adjectives transformed into their Comparative and Superlative Degrees?",
          optionA:
            "By adding -er or -r for Comparative, and -est or -st for Superlative.",
          optionB: "By doubling the last letter and adding -er or -est.",
          optionC: "By adding more for Comparative and most for Superlative.",
          correctAnswer:
            "By adding -er or -r for Comparative, and -est or -st for Superlative.",
        },
        {
          question:
            "When does the Positive Degree ending in 'e' transform into Comparative and Superlative Degrees?",
          optionA: "By adding -er and -est respectively.",
          optionB:
            "By changing 'e' to 'i' and adding -er and -est respectively.",
          optionC:
            "By doubling the last letter and adding -er and -est respectively.",
          correctAnswer: "By adding -er and -est respectively.",
        },
        {
          question:
            "How are adjectives with 'y' preceded by a consonant transformed into Comparative and Superlative Degrees?",
          optionA:
            "By changing 'y' to 'i' and adding -er and -est respectively.",
          optionB:
            "By doubling the last letter and adding -er and -est respectively.",
          optionC: "By adding more for Comparative and most for Superlative.",
          correctAnswer:
            "By changing 'y' to 'i' and adding -er and -est respectively.",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is the exception for forming Comparative and Superlative Degrees for some adjectives in the Positive Degree?",
          optionA:
            "By doubling the last letter and adding -er and -est respectively.",
          optionB: "By adding more for Comparative and most for Superlative.",
          optionC: "Irregular transformation.",
          correctAnswer: "Irregular transformation.",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which words use 'to' instead of 'than' when forming Comparative Degrees?",
          optionA: "elder, lower, upper",
          optionB: "junior, posterior, prior",
          optionC: "inner, interior, elder",
          correctAnswer: "junior, posterior, prior",
        },
        {
          question:
            "When do the words 'prefer' and 'preferable' use 'to' instead of 'than'?",
          optionA: "Always",
          optionB: "Never",
          optionC: "Occasionally",
          correctAnswer: "Always",
        },
      ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blank with correct option:",
    questions: [
        {
          question:
            "Children! You are already familiar with Scratch. In your previous class, you learnt about different types and shapes of blocks. Now in this chapter, you will learn a few more blocks which are Sensing, Variables and Conditional blocks.",
          optionA: "Motion",
          optionB: "Conditional",
          optionC: "Sound",
          correctAnswer: "Conditional",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Sensing block that prompts the user to type input using the keyboard is _________.",
          optionA: "mouse down?",
          optionB: "ask",
          optionC: "key space pressed?",
          correctAnswer: "ask",
        },
        {
          question:
            "To add a sensing block to a script, you should click on the Sensing blocks category and drag the ________ block to the coding area.",
          optionA: "mouse down?",
          optionB: "sensing",
          optionC: "ask",
          correctAnswer: "ask",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In Scratch, input is stored in the form of numbers, text, date, or pictures in ________.",
          optionA: "Variables",
          optionB: "Sensing",
          optionC: "Conditional",
          correctAnswer: "Variables",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In the Motion block, the value of the number of steps is not fixed and can be modified according to the ________.",
          optionA: "Sensing",
          optionB: "Script",
          optionC: "Conditional",
          correctAnswer: "Script",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Conditional blocks in Scratch are used when a task depends on certain ________.",
          optionA: "Sensing",
          optionB: "Variables",
          optionC: "Conditions",
          correctAnswer: "Conditions",
        },
        {
          question:
            "If, then ... else block in Scratch has two parts: ________.",
          optionA: "If and Only If",
          optionB: "If and Else",
          optionC: "Then and Else",
          correctAnswer: "Then and Else",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The task of eating an apple in the example given depends on the condition of ________.",
          optionA: "Mouse pointer",
          optionB: "Availability of apples",
          optionC: "Number of steps",
          correctAnswer: "Availability of apples",
        },
        {
          question:
            "To create a simple game in Scratch, you should choose ________ as the sprite and Neon Tunnel as the backdrop.",
          optionA: "Polar bear",
          optionB: "Button 5",
          optionC: "Sensing",
          correctAnswer: "Button 5",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In the game script, the sprite turns clockwise non-stop when the condition ________ is not fulfilled.",
          optionA: "Mouse pointer",
          optionB: "Any key pressed",
          optionC: "Sensing",
          correctAnswer: "Any key pressed",
        },
      ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
        {
          question:
            "Children will learn about Sensing, Variables, and Conditional blocks in Scratch.",
          optionA: "true",
          optionB: "false",
          correctAnswer: "true",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Sensing block prompts the user to type input using the keyboard.",
          optionA: "true",
          optionB: "false",
          correctAnswer: "true",
        },
        {
          question: "Variables in Scratch have fixed values.",
          optionA: "true",
          optionB: "false",
          correctAnswer: "false",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Conditional blocks are used in Scratch when a task depends on certain conditions.",
          optionA: "true",
          optionB: "false",
          correctAnswer: "true",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Motion block in Scratch has a fixed number of steps by default.",
          optionA: "true",
          optionB: "false",
          correctAnswer: "false",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The task of eating an apple in the given example depends on the availability of apples.",
          optionA: "true",
          optionB: "false",
          correctAnswer: "true",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The If then ... else block in Scratch has three parts: If, Then, and Else.",
          optionA: "true",
          optionB: "false",
          correctAnswer: "false",
        },
        {
          question: "India's road network is the largest in the world.",
          optionA: "true",
          optionB: "false",
          correctAnswer: "false",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Golden Quadrilateral connects the major metropolitan cities with a length of 5,846 kilometers.",
          optionA: "true",
          optionB: "false",
          correctAnswer: "true",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The first successful aeroplane was built in 1903 by the Wright brothers.",
          optionA: "true",
          optionB: "false",
          correctAnswer: "true",
        },
      ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
